export const boxingQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    questionText: 'Which boxer suffered his first professional loss to Muhammed Ali in Africa?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Mike Tyson',
      optionTwo: 'Larry Holmes',
      optionThree: 'George Foreman',
      optionFour: 'Trevor Berbick'
    },
    answer: 'George Foreman'
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    questionText: 'Which boxer retired with an Undefeated Status?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Mike Tyson',
      optionTwo: 'Larry Holmes',
      optionThree: 'Evander Holyfield',
      optionFour: 'Rocky Marciano'
    },
    answer: 'Rocky Marciano'
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    questionText: "Which boxing fight was deemed 'The Rumble in the Jungle'?",
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Mike Tyson vs Evander Holyfield',
      optionTwo: 'Larry Holmes vs Muhammed Ali',
      optionThree: 'George Foreman vs Muhammed Ali',
      optionFour: 'Floyd Mayweather vs Arturo Gatti'
    },
    answer: 'George Foreman vs Muhammed Ali'
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    questionText: 'Which boxer holds the record for being the oldest heavyweight boxing champion, winning the title at age 45?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Muhammed Ali',
      optionTwo: 'Lennox Lewis',
      optionThree: 'Sonny Liston',
      optionFour: 'George Foreman'
    },
    answer: 'George Foreman'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    questionText: 'Who currently holds the unified world heavyweight championship since 2021, and the Ring magazine title since 2022?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Tyson Fury',
      optionTwo: 'Oleksandr Usyk',
      optionThree: 'Daniel Dubois',
      optionFour: 'Anthony Joshua'
    },
    answer: 'Oleksandr Usyk'
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    questionText: 'How long does a boxing round last?',
    options: {
      optionOne: '2 Minutes',
      optionTwo: '5 Minutes',
      optionThree: '4 Minutes',
      optionFour: '3 Minutes'
    },
    answer: '3 Minutes'
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    questionText: 'Former Heavy weight Champion Anthony Joshua suffered his first professional loss to?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Wladimir Klitschko',
      optionTwo: 'Oleksandr Usyk',
      optionThree: 'Andy Ruiz Jr',
      optionFour: 'Daniel Dubois'
    },
    answer: 'Andy Ruiz Jr'
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    questionText: 'Which boxer is a two-weight undisputed champion in the "four-belt era"?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Terrence Crawford',
      optionTwo: 'Anthony Joshua',
      optionThree: 'Gervonta Davis',
      optionFour: 'Shakur Stevenson'
    },
    answer: 'Terrence Crawford'
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    questionText: 'Which boxer was formerly named "Cassius Marcellus Clay Jr?"',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Muhammed Ali',
      optionTwo: 'Lennox Lewis',
      optionThree: 'Mike Tyson',
      optionFour: 'Joe Frazier'
    },
    answer: 'Muhammed Ali'
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    questionText: 'Which boxer was nicknamed the Nigerian Nightmare?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Efe Ajagba',
      optionTwo: 'Samuel Peters',
      optionThree: 'Anthony Joshua',
      optionFour: 'Bash Alli'
    },
    answer: 'Samuel Peters'
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    questionText: 'Which boxer had the epiphet "THE GREATEST"?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Muhammed Ali',
      optionTwo: 'Lennox Lewis',
      optionThree: 'George Foreman',
      optionFour: 'Sonny Liston'
    },
    answer: 'Muhammed Ali'
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    questionText: 'Which boxer holds the record as the youngest boxer ever to win a heavyweight title',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Vitali Klitschko',
      optionTwo: 'Lennox Lewis',
      optionThree: 'Mike Tyson',
      optionFour: 'Ken Norton'
    },
    answer: 'Mike Tyson'
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    questionText: 'Which boxer holds the record for highest knockout to win ratio?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Artur Beterbeiv',
      optionTwo: 'Terrence Crawford',
      optionThree: 'Deontay Wilder',
      optionFour: 'Rocky Marciano'
    },
    answer: 'Deontay Wilder'
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    questionText: 'When a boxer falls to the floor, how many seconds do they have to get up again?',
    options: {
      optionOne: '15 seconds',
      optionTwo: '10 seconds',
      optionThree: '8 seconds',
      optionFour: '5 seconds'
    },
    answer: '10 seconds'
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    questionText: 'Which MMA fighter made his debut professional boxing match in 2017 against Floyd Mayweather Jr.?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Jon Jones',
      optionTwo: 'Brock Lesnar',
      optionThree: 'Max Holloway',
      optionFour: 'Conor McGregor'
    },
    answer: 'Conor McGregor'
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    questionText: 'What is the name for the boxing stance where the left foot is placed in front of the right foot?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Orthodox Stance',
      optionTwo: 'Southpaw Stance',
      optionThree: 'Unorthodox Stance',
      optionFour: 'Lefted Stance'
    },
    answer: 'Orthodox Stance'
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    questionText: 'What is the term for the technique where a boxer leans against the ropes of the ring and allows blows to be absorbed by the ropes’ elasticity, tiring out the boxer throwing the punches?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Rope-A-Dope',
      optionTwo: 'Lean-Dodge technique',
      optionThree: 'Round-the-twist',
      optionFour: 'Slip-Roll Technique'
    },
    answer: 'Rope-A-Dope'
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    questionText: 'What is the nickname of Tyson Fury?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Fury of the Gods',
      optionTwo: 'Mountain Man',
      optionThree: 'The Gypsy King',
      optionFour: 'Iron Fury'
    },
    answer: 'The Gypsy King'
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    questionText: 'Who was the first light heavyweight champion to defeat a heavyweight champion?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Mickey Walker',
      optionTwo: 'Michael Spinks',
      optionThree: 'Archie Moore',
      optionFour: 'Floyd Patterson'
    },
    answer: 'Michael Spinks'
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    questionText: 'Who claimed to “float like a butterfly, sting like a bee”?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Muhammed Ali',
      optionTwo: 'Larry Holmes',
      optionThree: 'George Foreman',
      optionFour: 'Evander Holyfield'
    },
    answer: 'Muhammed Ali'
  },
]